Meat.
Well, well, well. What do you think?
Looks so good!
Let's cut it up.
Chopped
It's not for chopping, but it's easy to chop.
It's okay, I'm fine.
I'm not such a novice.
Maybe you're a peer or something.
I'm not that unfamiliar
You there who's chillin'
I'm fine.
I was trying too hard.
I got a bean on my hand, and I made a fire.
It was really hard today.
Why was today so hard?
It was really hard.
Oh, my God, A-chan.
Aachan.
Hey!
Here's the olive oil.
Because I...
This level
box
I would add salt and pepper.
I don't have salt and pepper.
I have no salt and pepper.
Isn't it pretty big no salt and pepper?
I think I'll put in some bling.
I don't have a theory about what I could do if I put in a blinge.
It's like a cyclone.
Look at these beans.
Pien.
New Clicking.
Papa, papa.
Hee-hee.
I'll put it in.
Like this.
Here.
Various
There are many ways to make it
Delicious.
It's good.
Good!
Thank you for dinner.
Thank you for watching
I didn't have شي, so I cut it with بال water.
I forgot.
ALERT
This is about right?
Okay, here we go.
Let's get some light on this.
I can do it.
It's bigger than usual.
I think it's seething.
Good night.
Mayo... it's good.
Hey, I'm gonna start with this one in the open.
Open.
Oh!
I'll see you later.
Looks good!
I just bought some cheese to avoid.
I'll put it in.
I thought of that.
Yum!
Oh my God!
I can't run.
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
It's absolutely delicious!
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
I'm gonna have to roll some more.
You're gonna take that?
You're taking that one.
It's totally hot.
Let's go get a marshmallow.
Okay, I'll have one.
Well, well, well. Let's see what you got.
Open.
Looks so good!
Oh my God!
Lots of calories!
Looks so good!
Let's eat!
Bon appétit!
Let's eat it right away!
Looks so delicious!
Bon appétit!Bon appétit!
Looks amazing.
Are you sure about the seasoning?
I haven't tasted it or anything.
Bon appétit.
Thank you for watching.
This is, this is bad. Bad food.
Delicious.
I just left the fire.
I'll take it right here.
It's cold away from the fire.
The meat and cheese is absolutely delicious!
Look at this happy spoon!
It's absolutely hot already, isn't it?
That's all for today.
See you soon.
Bye.
Oh, my God!
It's too good!
And you know, when you cook something like ootou...
If you can't finish it, you know...
I put it in a water bottle and take it home.
It looks so good!
I can eat all of this.
I can drink it all.
Thank you for the food.
Thank you for watching.
I'm jealous.
I mean, this is kree.
Whoever got to eat the food will be even hungrier.
I feel bad.
I'm eating this.
It's not at night.
I'm eating like a normal uncle.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I'm the one who found it and put on the steak mascot.
This cup has been dann for over 90 years.
I'd rather
Thank you for the food! It was so good!
Did I not see your face the whole time?
It was so good!
I'm so happy today!
I actually bought taiyaki.
I was thinking of grilling them in my hot sandwich maker.
But I'm satisfied and I'm tired today.
I'm going home now.
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you for watching!
See you soon!
Bye-bye!
Bye bye!
Thank you all for watching!
I've been working really, really hard to get the fire started.
Hey, guys, please click the "like" button.
Hang in there a little bit, and please like us!
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel!